A Guide to the Virginia Chapter of the National Organization for Women Records, 1971-2004, 2011
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Chapter of the National Organization for Women Records, 1971-2004, 2011
The Library of Virginia
43458
To be added.
National Organization for Women. Virginia. Chapter.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
THIS COLLECTION IS CURRENTLY BEING PROCESSED. ANTICIPATED OPENING OF COLLECTION JUNE 2013.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Virginia NOW, 18 September 2007 (43458).
Gift of Virginia NOW, 15 December 2008 (44064).
Gift of Virginia NOW, 20 September 2011 (50175).
All gifts care of Lee Perkins, Alexandria. The three accessions are filed jointly under accession number 43458.
Biographical Information
To be added.
Scope and Content
To be added.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Virginia NOW records
Series II. Newsletters and local chapter files
Series III. Frances Hicks papers
Series IV. Audiovisual materials
Contents List
- Series I. Virginia NOW Records, 1971-2004, 2011. (Box 1-13)
  Scope and Content note to be added.
  Arrangement info to be added.
  - Abortion, 1973-1975, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abortion, 1984-1986. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abortion, 1987. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abortion, 1988. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abortion, 1989. (Box 1, Folder 5-7)
  - Abortion, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 8-11)
  - Abortion, 1991. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Abortion, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Abortion, 1993-1994. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Abortion, 1997-1999. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Abortion, 2002-2003. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Administrative and general files, 1971-1973. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Administrative and general files, 1974. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Includes an introductory handbook to the National Organization for Women (apparently produced by the Capitol Hill Chapter), listing its national board, task forces, by-laws, and accomplishments of the group from 1966-1973.
  - Administrative and general files, 1975. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Administrative and general files, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    In part consists of various letters and other documents pertaining to controversy over a vote, taken at the National Board meeting on 5-6 June 1976, to invalidate the Southern Regional Conference, held that April 24-25.
  - Administrative and general files, 1977. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Includes a copy of The First Women's State of the Union Address, delivered by Karen DeCrow, president of the National Organization for Women.
  - Administrative and general files, 1978. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Administrative and general files, 1979. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Administrative and general files, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Administrative and general files, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Administrative and general files, 1982. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Includes documents pertaining to the formal incorporation of Virginia NOW under 501(c)(4) tax exempt status.
  - Administrative and general files, 1983. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Administrative and general files, 1983. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Includes manual entitled NOW Guidelines for Feminist Consciousness-Raising.
  - Administrative and general files, 1984. (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
    Consists in large part of papers related to State Council and Executive Committee business.
  - Administrative and general files, 1985. (Box 3, Folder 4-7)
    Consists in large part of papers related to State Council and Executive Committee business, and Virginia NOW's 3 March 1985 "Women In Aviation" brunch.
  - Administrative and general files, 1986. (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
    Consists in large part of papers related to State Council and Executive Committee business, and Virginia NOW's 2 March 1986 "Women in the Arts" brunch.
  - Administrative and general files, 1987. (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    Consists in large part of papers related to State Council and Executive Committee business, and Virginia NOW's 1 March 1987 "Women in the Law" brunch.
  - Administrative and general files (Employment Committee), 1987-1991. (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
    A series of files pertaining to the work of the Virginia NOW Employment Committee (also referred to as the Personnel Committee), chiefly focused on rules and guidelines for hiring, supervising, and terminating employment of the Virginia NOW Staff Person, along with documentation of the performance of the person who held that position during this time period.
  - Administrative and general files, 1988. (Box 4, Folder 5-9)
    Consists in large part of papers related to State Council and Executive Committee business, Virginia NOW's 24 April 1988 "Women in Politics" brunch, fundraising, and membership recruitment. Includes copies of the Virginia NOW Canvassing Manual.
  - Administrative and general files, 1989. (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Administrative and general files, 1989. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Fundraising files.
  - Administrative and general files, 1989-1990. (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
    Membership polls.
  - Administrative and general files, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7-10)
    Consists in large part of papers related to State Council and Executive Committee business, Virginia NOW's 31 March 1990 "Women in the Arts" dinner, and leadership and chapter development.
  - Administrative and general files, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Administrative and general files, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
    Files documenting problems with the Virginia NOW co-Legislative Coordinator, and attempts to bring about her removal from office.
  - Administrative and general files, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Files documenting Virginia NOW's work with an outside consultant on the topic of organizational development.
  - Administrative and general files, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
    Consists in large part of papers related to State Council and Executive Committee business, including financial reports. Also includes a copy of the August 1991 Virginia NOW Administrative Manual and the September 1991 Virginia NOW Policy Manual.
  - Administrative and general files, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
    Consists in large part of papers related to State Council and Executive Committee business, financial reports, and other matters. Also includes two drafts of a 1992 update to the Virginia NOW Policy Manual.
  - Administrative and general files, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Administrative and general files, 1994. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Includes a copy of the 1994-1995 edition of the Virginia NOW Policy Manual.
  - Administrative and general files, 1995-1999. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Files for this time period are minimal, and miscellaneous in nature.
  - Administrative and general files, 1995-2003. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Scattered files related to Take Back the Night events around Virginia.
  - Administrative and general files, 2000-2004. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Files for this time period are minimal, and miscellaneous in nature. Includes a small sample of State Council documentation from 2003, and a copy of the Student Action Committee Organizing Handbook, produced by the Pennsylvania NOW Education Fund in 1998.
  - Administrative and general files, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Program and fliers for the NOW Mid-Atlantic Feminist Festival and Conference, held in Norfolk.
  - Administrative and general files, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Program, fliers, and other papers related to the Second Annual Mid-Atlantic Feminist Festival (held in Virginia Beach), which also served as that year's Virginia NOW Annual Conference.
  - Administrative and general files, undated. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    A handful of miscellaneous papers, undated but likely created in the 1970's and 1980's. Includes a flier entitled Why Feminists Want Child Care, another entitled Help De-Sexigrate the Jaycees, and a sexuality survey produced by the New York City Chapter of NOW.
  - Clippings, 1973-1975. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1976-1978. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1972-1975. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1976. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1977. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1978. (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1979. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1981. (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1983-1994. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Issues, 1973. (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
    Topics include women's health, aging, the availability of credit to women, and sex-role stereotypes in textbooks used in the Lincoln, Nebraska, public school system (a study produced by the Lincoln chapter of NOW). Also includes a transcript of Betty Friedan's Feminist Community Press Conference, given in New York City on 7 March 1973, and a copy of a bill (H.R. 4034) presented to the U.S. House of Representatives to carry out the recommendations of the Presidential Task Force on Women's Rights and Responsibilities.
  - Issues, 1974. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Topics include the work of the NOW Women and Arts Task Force, and efforts to have Susan B. Anthony's birthday made a national holiday.
  - Issues, 1975. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Topics include rape and sexual assault, violent pornography, the legal rights of women in marriage and divorce, and the United Nations Conference on Women, held in Mexico City.
  - Issues, 1976. (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
    Topics include homosexual rights, marital rape, venereal disease, the availability of credit to women, the status of the women's movement, and the International Women's Year Conference in Virginia. Includes newsletters from the Women's Division of the State of New York and the Washington (D.C.) Area Feminist Federal Credit Union,
  - Issues, 1977. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Topics include the implications of flexitime for working women. Also includes a copy of De-Mystifying The Lavender Menace: A NOW Primer on Lesbian-Baiting, published by the NOW National Task Force on Sexuality and Lesbianism, and a booklet entitled Women In Politics, produced by the Women's Program, Office of Equal Opportunity, Smithsonian Institution.
  - Issues, 1978. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Topics include sex role stereotypes in the television industry, and minority participation in government.
  - Issues, 1979. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Topics include the treatment of women under the social security system. Also includes a file on a woman who filed a complaint of sex discrimination against the Staunton Correctional Center, with whom she was employed as a correctional officer, and another on a woman seeking legal aid in a divorce case.
  - Issues, 1980. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Topics include a class action suit dealing with sex discrimination in hiring by federal highway construction contractors, opposition to reinstatement of the draft, and the White House Conference on Families.
  - Issues, 1981. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Topics include lesbianism and lesbian rights, equal pay, and labor unionization.
  - Issues, 1983. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Topics include female prisoners of conscience in foreign countries,
  - Issues, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Topics include a woman's rights in a divorce case, an all-male political "roast" in Virginia Beach featuring female exotic dancers, and reform of sexual assault law.
  - Issues, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Topics include a female employee's claims of offenses including sex and age discrimination, wrongful termination, and violation of the Equal Pay Act against Air France.
  - Issues, 1988. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Topics include spousal support, and the case of a woman jailed for contempt of court when she refused the reveal her daughter's whereabouts, in an effort to protect her from the father accused of raping her.
  - Issues, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
    Topics include a sex discrimination suit filed by employees of the University of Virginia Health Sciences Center, sex discrimination litigation against the Virginia Military Institute, the Supreme Court nomination of Judge David Souter, fair housing, the Virginia Test Bias Advisory Committee, child sexual assault, domestic violence, and interest by some in NOW to start a third political party.
  - Issues, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Topics include the Supreme Court nomination of Judge Clarence Thomas, and domestic violence.
  - Issues, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Topics include workforce diversity, attempts by another group to ban a gay newspaper from the Fairfax County Library system, Virginia women in history,
  - Issues, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Topics include nuclear weapons and public housing for senior citizens. Also includes literature from the Draft and Military Project.
  - Issues, 1994. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Topics include domestic violence, education, and mentally disabled citizens.
  - Issues, 1997-1999. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Topics include abuse against women by military personnel and body image. Also includes packets from a National Association of Commissions for Women legislative briefing on "Women and the 106th Congress" and a briefing of the same group by the White House's Office for Women's Initiatives and Outreach on "Supporting Women and Families: President Clinton's Accomplishments and Agenda."
  - Issues, 2002-2003, 2008. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Topics include domestic violence and sexual assault, discrimination against female employees of Wal-Mart, human rights issues, and poverty.
  - Legislative Office, 1973-1977. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Includes alerts and lobbying strategies regarding abortion rights, and copies of statements made by NOW representatives on the topics of the Fair Labor Standards Act and the nomination of Judge John Paul Stevens to the Supreme Court.
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1979. (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
    The Virginia NOW PAC was established in 1979.
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1980. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1981. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1982. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1983. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1984. (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
    Includes two drafts of the Virginia NOW Political Action Committee (PAC) Guide for Activists.
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1985. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1987. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1988. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1989. (Box 11, Folder 4-6)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 7-10)
    Includes copy of the Official PAC Manual, revised February 1990.
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Includes copy of the Virginia NOW Political Action Committee (PAC) Guide for Activists, September 1993 update/revision.
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1994. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Includes copy of the Virginia NOW Legislative Action Guide to the Virginia General Assembly, June 1994 update.
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 1996-1999. (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 2000-2004. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - PAC and miscellaneous legislative/political files, 2011. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - State Conference, 1977, 1979. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - State Conference, 1981, 1982. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - State Conference, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - State Conference, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - State Conference, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 13-14)
  - State Conference, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - State Conference, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - State Conference, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
  - State Conference, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - State Conference, 1994. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - State Conference, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Program, fliers, and other papers related to the Second Annual Mid-Atlantic Feminist Festival (held in Virginia Beach), which also served as that year's Virginia NOW State Conference.
  - State Conference, 2003. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - State Conference, 2004. (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Series II. Newsletters and local chapter files, 1973-2004. (Box 13-19)
  - Alexandria chapter, 1975, 1977, 1981-1983. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Alexandria chapter, 1991-1994, 1996-2001. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Issues of the Alexandria NOW Newsletter (1991-1994) and later the Chapter News newsletter (1996-2001, which covered the Alexandria, Arlington, Northern Virginia, and Prince William County chapters (but only the Alexandria, Arlington, and Northern Virginia chapters from the September/October 1999 issue forward).
  - Alexandria chapter, 1997-2000. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Allegheny Highlands chapter, 1982-1991. (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    Binder (deconstructed) containing newspaper clippings, photographs, correspondence, and other material related to the chapter.
  - Allegheny Highlands chapter, 1982-1991. (Box 14, Folder 3-9)
    A second binder (deconstructed) containing various records of the chapter along with literature from Virginia and National NOW.
  - Allegheny Highlands chapter, 1982-1984, 1997-1998. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Arlington chapter, 1981-1984, 1989-2001. (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    Includes copies of the chapter's Arlington NOW Newsbreaks newsletter. See also Alexandria chapter newsletter file, as Arlington was included in the joint newsletter Chapter News.
  - Charlottesville chapter, 1974. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Mock-up and final, printed booklet entitled What Do You Say, Sister? produced by the Charlotesville NOW Task Force on the Image of Women in response to a guest editorial in the Washington Post in which the writer wished for a book giving responses for sexist remarks.
  - Charlottesville chapter, 1975-1978, 1981-1982. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Issues of the chapter's Charlottesville NOW newsletter.
  - Charlottesville chapter, 1983-1984, 1991, 1994. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Charlottesville chapter, 1979-1984. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Chesterfield County chapter, 1983-1984. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Danville chapter, 1979, 1981. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - D.C./National Capitol Area chapter 1973. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Dulles Area chapter, 1981-1984, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Includes issues of the chapter's Dulles Area NOW News newsletter.
  - Epsilon Rho Alpha chapter, 1979. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Fredericksburg chapter, 1980-1983, 1989. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Includes issues of the chapter's Fredericksburg Area NOW (1980-1983) and NOW in the Fredericksburg Area (1989) newsletters.
  - Harrisonburg-Rockingham chapter, 1979-1985. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Includes copies of the chapter's Harrisonburg-Rockingham NOW newsletter.
  - James Madison University chapter, 1985. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Lynchburg chapter, 1977, 1980-1984. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Issues of the chapter's NOWadays newsletter.
  - Lynchburg/Sweet Briar chapter, 1997-2004. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Mary Washington College chapter, 1997-2002. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Montgomery County chapter, 1980, 1989-1991. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Montgomery County chapter, 1995-1998. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Includes issues of the chapter's Viewpoints newsletter.
  - Montgomery County chapter, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Montgomery County chapter, 2000-2004. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Nelson County chapter, 2001-2004. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - New River Valley chapter, 1976, 1980. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Northern Shenandoah chapter, 1998-2001. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Northern Virginia (NOVA) chapter, 1973-1974. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Issues of the Northern Virginia chapter newsletter in its early, unnamed form, and later under the title Equal Times.
  - Northern Virginia (NOVA) chapter, 1975. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Issues of the chapter's Equal Times newsletter.
  - Northern Virginia (NOVA) chapter, 1976. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Northern Virginia (NOVA) chapter, 1977-1978. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Northern Virginia (NOVA) chapter, 1981-1984. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Issues of the chapter's NOVA NOW and Northern Virginia NOW newsletters.
  - Northern Virginia (NOVA) chapter, 1977-1981. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Northern Virginia (NOVA) chapter, 1996-2003. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NOW National Labor Task Force newsletter, The Organizer, November 1975. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - NOW (National) newsletter, Do It Now, 1973-1974. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NOW (National) newsletter, Do It Now, 1975-1977. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - NOW (National) newsletter, Do It Now, March 1979. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - NOW National Task Force on Sexuality and Lesbianism newsletter, [1973?] and NOW Sexuality Task Force newsletter, January 1976. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - NOW National Task Force on Women and Poverty newsletter, Common Wealth, September 1975. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Old Dominion University chapter, 2003-2004. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Peninsula chapter, 1980-1983. (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
  - Prince William County/Western Prince William County chapter, 1973-1976. (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
    Includes issues of Prince William County and Western Prince William County NOW newsletters, 1975-1976 (folder 9).
  - Prince William County chapter, 1981-1984. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Issues of the chapter's NOW & Then Times newsletter.
  - Prince William County chapter, 1998-2004. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Richmond chapter, 1973-2002. (Box 17, Folder 12-14)
    Includes issues of the unnamed Richmond NOW newsletter.
  - Roanoke Valley chapter, 1975-1976. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Includes issues of the chapter's Moving, newsletter.
  - Roanoke Valley chapter, 1981-1984. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Includes issues of the chapter's Equal Times newsletter.
  - Roanoke Valley chapter, 1997-2002. (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
  - Rockbridge Valley chapter, 1983, 1997-2004. (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
    Includes issues of the chapter's Valley Voice newsletter.
  - Shenandoah Valley chapter, 1982. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Staunton chapter, 2000-2003. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Tidewater chapter, 1993-1995. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Tidewater chapter, 1996-2000. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Tidewater chapter, 2001-2003. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Tidewater chapter, 1992-1993. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Issues of the chapter's NOW or Never newsletter.
  - Tidewater chapter, 1994-1995 (Feb). (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Tidewater chapter, March-December 1995. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Tidewater chapter, January-June 1996. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Tidewater chapter, July-December 1996. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Tidewater chapter, 1997. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Tidewater chapter, 1998-2000. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Issues of the chapter's NOW or Never, Here and NOW, and NOW and Again newsletters.
  - Tidewater chapter, 2001-2002. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Issues of the chapter's Here and NOW, NOW is the Time, and The Time is NOW newsletters.
  - Tri-Cities chapter, undated. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - University of Virginia chapter, 1997-2003. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - University of Virginia's College at Wise chapter, 2003. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Vienna chapter, 1999-2003. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Highlands chapter, 1980-1984. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Includes issues of the chapter's untitled newsletter, 1983-1984.
  - Virginia Highlands chapter, 1997-2004. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Virginia NOW newsletter, Virginia NOW or Never, [1975]. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Virginia NOW newsletter, Yes Virginia, [1979]. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Virginia NOW newsletter, Virginia NOW, 1982-1986. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Virginia NOW newsletter, Virginia NOW Choices (oversize) 1986-1989. (Box 20, Folder 1)